{
    "subject": "resource/Philip_Rivers",
    "predicate": "property/college",
    "object": "resource/NC_State_Wolfpack_football",
    "human_readable": "Philip Rivers attended NC State Wolfpack football.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8699396848678589,
            "question": "Which team did Philip Rivers play for at NC State?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8396233320236206,
            "question": "In what activity was Philip Rivers involved at NC State?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8370503187179565,
            "question": "What sport did Philip Rivers play at NC State?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7792026996612549,
            "question": "What team represented Philip Rivers during his time at NC State?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.666334331035614,
            "question": "Is Philip Rivers known for playing football?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5696665644645691,
            "question": "What university did Philip Rivers attend?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5414793491363525,
            "question": "Where did Philip Rivers play college football?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43637746572494507,
            "question": "Did Philip Rivers participate in sports while in college?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3918387293815613,
            "question": "Was Philip Rivers involved in collegiate athletics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31668615341186523,
            "question": "What is the name of the football team at NC State?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Philip Rivers attended NC State Wolfpack football.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3981_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Philip Rivers involved in collegiate athletics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3981_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Philip Rivers participate in sports while in college?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3981_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Philip Rivers play college football?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3981_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3981_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3981_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3981_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3981_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3981_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3981_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3981_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3981_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3981_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3981_64.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide multiple references to Philip Rivers attending North Carolina State University and playing for the NC State Wolfpack football team, supporting this statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}